articles2use.com 2007-12-27

# Article Directory | Submit Articles | FREE Content | Marketing & SEO

Welcome to the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") for 'Articles2Use.com'. The services available at 'Articles2Use.com' are provided by 'Articles2Use.com' ('Articles2Use.com', 'we', 'us' or 'our') located in Northamptonshire, UK. 

Your privacy is very important to us. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. If you have additional questions about Articles2Use.com's general privacy principles, please contact us. 

This Privacy Policy applies from 6th December 2007 for new registering users. 

**Overview**

By accepting this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. If you object to this use and disclosure please do not register with us. 

This Privacy Policy contains a number of references to other pages on our Site and other websites. Please note: underlined words and phrases are click-through links to these pages and websites. 'Articles2Use.com' strongly recommends that you click on such links to obtain further important details about the Privacy Policy, as they may contain further terms and conditions which apply to you as an 'Articles2Use.com' member. 

Please note that your Information will be stored and processed on our computers in the UK. The laws on holding personal data in countries other than the UK may be less stringent than the laws applicable to the UK but 'Articles2Use.com' will hold and transmit your information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. 'Articles2Use.com' will never sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. 

This Privacy Policy applies to the 'Articles2Use.com' UK website (the "Site"). 

**Contents**

1\. Information We Collect 2\. Our Use of Your Information 3\. Our Disclosure of Your Information 4\. Control of Your Password 5\. Accessing, Reviewing, and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information 6\. Other Information Collectors 7\. Security 8\. Notice 

**1\. Information We Collect**

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, efficient, and personalised experience. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for this purpose. 

In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to use our services, we may require you to provide contact, identity and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option not to provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature. 

We use this personal information in order that we can contact you should it become necessary. 

We DO NOT use data collection devices such as "cookies" on the Site. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that could be used to obtain other information such as your browsing habits. We will NOT be collecting any information other than as stated above. 

Although we WILL NOT be using cookies, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Site that are placed by third parties. For example, if you view a web page created by an advertiser or other user, which is external to this site, there may be a "cookie" placed within that web page. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

**2\. Our Use of Your Information**

We use information in the files we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site, to resolve disputes, provide customer support, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. At times, we may examine your information to identify users using multiple Usernames or aliases. 

You agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to analyse site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customise the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs. 

You agree that we may use your information to contact you if necessary regarding your account and / or any suspicious activities therein. By accepting the terms and conditions and reading this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, please do not register with us. 

If you send an email to us, we do not use that email address for any purpose other than for the purpose stated above. We do not rent or sell these email addresses. 

**3\. Our Disclosure of Your Information**

As a matter of policy, 'Articles2Use.com' will never sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. However, the following describes some of the ways that we may disclose your personally identifiable information. 

(a) Some of your personal details (such as your author name, for example) are displayed throughout the Site and are therefore available to the public. Therefore, any of the people you have revealed this information to, will be able to personally identify you on the 'Articles2Use.com' Site. If you are an article publisher, you should be aware that your author name is available to view openly on the Site and that it is highly likely (although not obligatory) that your email address will become known to others if you reply via email to any contacts you may get. Further, we may send out notices to you or other members regarding suspicious activity or policy violations on the Site. 

(b) Legal Requests. 'Articles2Use.com' cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties, to enforce laws and third party rights, such as intellectual property rights and laws relating to fraud. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials such as a Section 29 (3) Data Protection Act 1998 form relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, or other activity that may expose us or you to legal liability, we can (and you authorise us to) disclose personal information such as name, telephone number, email address, Username history, and article listing history about you as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. 

We cannot ensure that all of your communications with 'Articles2Use.com' and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or communications with 'Articles2Use.com' will always remain private. 

**4\. Control of Your Password**

You are responsible for all actions taken with your Username and password, including those actions that result in fees being charged to your account. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your 'Articles2Use.com' password to any third parties. If you choose to share your Username and password or your information with third parties to where it is necessary for you to do so for them to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your Username and password and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password or account has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password as detailed in Section 6 below. 

**5\. Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information**

We offer you the ability to automatically review and change the information you submit to us by logging into the Site and entering in the new information yourself. Generally, we will not modify your personal information based on your request because it is very difficult to authenticate your account manually. You can change your Username, password, contact information, by logging in and going to the relevant section. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. 

Upon your emailed request, we will deactivate your account and contact information from our active databases. To make this request, please contact us. Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible in accordance with any applicable laws. 

We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored "back up" systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. 

**6\. Other Information Collectors**

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are advertisers or publishers on the Site or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since 'Articles2Use.com' does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

**7\. Security**

'Articles2Use.com' treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorised access. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. 

**8\. Notice**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time in order that it accurately reflects the regulatory environment and our own data collection and disclosure practices. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site. In addition, we will notify you by posting the amended Privacy Policy on the Site.
